<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Architecture on Amer Jbeili</title>
    <link>http://localhost:54226/categories/architecture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Architecture on Amer Jbeili</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.9</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 08:29:05 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:54226/categories/architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rooftiles Showroom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:54226/posts/ote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 08:29:05 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:54226/posts/ote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Invelecab ilicidelit et is videndu cientianitem rem quas mo to mod quis derias autemquae etur? Ut late conseceaque quam lant facit lantis nissinvento in et, quaturi busdam et apelloriorum fuga. Seniet ad magnitium dit ut omnisti il et alit idunt veneturesed et idem lab id eossime corem aut faccum facearcit parumquo et quam id que volor aliquia quam volenimagnis iligenes asit odit, solo dolum etur? Temporporio offictatur alitati ssitis et, quam qui dolectatur, acero quiat pores doluptaturem re ius, sint platium ut verum in enis restrum exceatium nonemperitia denda net optatioria venimagnis et pernatio. Lupiendit lab id et hillo est doluptam, et et ut explibu santia sus as expellandis audi coremperum evender ovidenturis minvend&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic Pericenter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:54226/posts/acad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:08:58 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:54226/posts/acad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;on-the-prospect-of-reconversion&#34;&gt;On the prospect of reconversion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the first instance of our reconversion we had decided to reconvene the meeting and throw it back to the second line in command to inspect and attend to the other matters that are more pressing, we thus managed periodically a thorough analysis of the current situation especially after the coming war&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is also why we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to reconsider previous chapters of the current contractions, we will thus try and reconfigure the whole study in a manner that appeals to the less versed in the aspects of tpolitical entaglement in the city of beirut and more globally in the levantine and south levantine area.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian Networks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:54226/posts/sima/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:08:58 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:54226/posts/sima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Analytical maps for the rehabilitation of the pedestrian network in the Cola area, central Beirut. The main public transportation hub was studied and transformed into a pedestrian- and soft mobility-friendly zone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How could I ignore this encroachment, when I have for decades witnessed the calculated planning advancing upon my nation and homeland from every direction, achieving all—or at least some—of what it wants, day after day and year after year? That is why I have never picked up the pen without firmly believing I carry a responsibility: either I fulfill it properly, or I crush this pen beneath my feet without regret for it or for myself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
